degiro.co.uk 2019-09-13

# Privacy & Cookies

Who do we have personal data from?

We can have (some) personal data of anyone who has contact with DEGIRO. If you request additional information we will store the information which is provided during that request.

We are required by law to have personal information surrounding all of our clients. This information is gathered during the registration and requested when necessary. In some cases it may be necessary for us to make use of third parties to either verify or collect information. 

What personal data is collected?

_Data about you_

This includes your name, address, telephone number and email address. In the event you are a corporate client we will also collect information surrounding your company or foundation. If you open a minor account or a joint account, the information surrounding the secondary account holders will also be collected. We will also ask for copies of your ID and personal numbers such as your tax identification number or relevant identifiers.

_Transaction history_

In addition to personal data which DEGIRO have in relation to clients, we also keep a historic log concerning transaction and order history.

_Contact history_

We keep record of the times when you have contacted DEGIRO, this includes telephone recordings, emails or other ways you have communicated with us.

_Website visits and app use_

In the event that you visit the website of DEGIRO, we will also collect the IP address which is used. Should your IP address be used, for example via Google Analytics this will be done in an anonymised way.

_External data sources_

There are times where DEGIRO will use external data provides, such as checking with the relevant chamber of commerce or in the event a credit check is required.

In the event that DEGIRO carry out credit checks (BKR) they apply the strictest confidentiality on this information. Any individual who has access to this information does so only in the performance of their duty and the relevant data protection regulation is fully complied with. In the event you have questions of when BKR checks are carried out please contact the service desk of DEGIRO.

_Sensitive personal data_

Sensitive personal data include things such as tax identification number, criminal history, biometric data, political beliefs, sexuality or ethnic origin, etc. If processing sensitive personal data is necessary, there are stricter rules applied to this. 

At DEGIRO we never use sensitive data related to health, religious beliefs, political or philosophical beliefs, sexual orientation or ethnic origin.

We have a legal obligation to identify our clients, therefore we require the tax identification number to do this.
